# AELON FARKASH

INDUSTRIAL DESIGNER



#### **Personal Profile**

Industrial designer, controls the full cycle of product generation, starting from the idea, research, specification, concept design (sketching, drawing, rendering), design and prototype (3D printed model) and transfer to production. worked with injection molding, CNC manufacturing, product 3D design, 3D printing and animation.

#### CONTACT



#### Address

Ha-Meri 14 Givatayim Israel



#### mail

aelonfarkash@gmail.com



#### Phone

+9720546397082



#### Portfolio

www.instagram.com/kyoo12

#### WORK EXPERIENCE

#### VARIOUS DESIGN PROJECTS ISRAEL/ 2020 - 2021

Design research and 3D printing of models per clients request

- Designed and conceptualized the perfect project for each client.
- · Visited job sites to get measurements for accuracy and precision.
- · Created detailed CAD drawings, 3d models and product rendering.
- Designed models for architecture students for FDM printing

# STUDENT JOBS FLORENCE ITALY / 2017 - 2020

Conducted an array of projects including furniture upholstery, woodworking, 3D home rendering and interior items manufacturing using the flowing methods

- cnc
- Welding
- Investment casting
- Injection molding
- Glass blowing
- Stem bending
- DLP printing for prototyping
- Laser cut and fabrication

#### TOOLS

























## EDUCATION

### European Bachelor of Science in design

Accademia Italiana di arte/Florence IT/2017 - 2020

MAIN COURSES -Product design , Model building, Architect for interiors, Technology of materials, Digital modeling, Urban design

#### KEY PROJECTS

3D printed adaptive shoe sole, Bioluminescent alga lamp EARLY STUDIES

2013 combat medic course in the IDF 2012 Dror Israel a year of informal education 2011 finished high school Ort Hashomron (biology 5 units, English 7 units)

# A

# AELON FARKASH

INDUSTRIAL DESIGNER

#### Technical skills

- Sketching
- Material Selection
- Prototyping
- Manufacturing

- Typography
- Branding
- Assembly Protoco
- Graphic design

- Motion Graphics
- Art Direction
- Marketing

#### PRE-STUDY WORK

#### BARISTA

Benedict/Tell Aviv / 2016- 2017

#### BAR TENDER

Koli Alma/ Tell Aviv / 2016- 2017

# STRENGTHS

USER CENTERED DESIGN
STRATEGIC THINKING
SPEAKING AND PRESENTATION
VISUAL COMMUNICATION

## ARMY SERVICE

#### NAHAL BRIGADE/ 2012 - 2016

- Combat medic
- · Educational corp guide

#### SOCIAL SERVICES

Dror Israel/ 2006 - 2016

- Training and management positions and accompanying training teams
- Management of various projects such as community volunteer and enterprises at the municipal and district level
- Execution of multiple trips and seminars planing, budgeting and recruiting